Can you hear me?
Hey, can you hear me?
Can you...
August... 4th.
Hey, you.
Hey, what's wrong?
I heard a scream. Are you all right?
Someone will be coming for you soon.
Um...
Now.
Be patient and wait.
Who is she?
I wonder who's coming for you.
Are you all right?
You suddenly collapsed, so I was worried.
What's all this about you collapsing?
Who is he?
Hey,
are you really all right?
I don't know this person.
I'll walk you home,
so hurry up and get ready.
At least answer me.
Yes.
Yes?
I heard you collapsed.
Toma, why are you here, too?
Because Sawa contacted me.
Are you all right? You didn't
hit anything, did you?
What are you spacing out for?
Are you listening to what we're saying?
Shin, don't pressure her like that.
She just woke up. What do you expect?
I know you're worried.
Now, before we go home,
should we stop by the hospital?
We probably should.
Y-Yes.
You can't!
You can't go to the hospital.
It'll be a huge hassle.
Just tell them you're sleepy and pretend.
Yes.
So we're going to the hospital.
No.
Which is it?
I think I'm just tired.
I'll go home.
If you were so tired you fell over,
what kind of lifestyle do you lead?
You're always—
Now, now.
If that's all it is, we'll take you home.
We're not walking too fast, are we?
No.
It's getting cold.
It's only August. What's
going on with this weather?
Just when you think
the wet season's over,
summer has passed you by, and it's fall.
By the way, Shin, what
happened to prep school?
I left early.
Is it okay for an exam student to do that?
I'm doing what needs to be done,
even without you telling me to.
Man, you're such an uncute little brother.
I've told you before,
you're not my older brother.
This part of him hasn't changed
since he was a kid, right?
Weren't you listening?
I can't keep up with the conversation.
I'm acquainted with these people,
but I can't remember.
Hey, I think she...
Lay off already.
Stop acting like an old woman.
Nothing.
Old woman?
You're meddlesome. Like an old woman.
I'm just worried about her.
Besides, you...
There's nothing.
It's none of your business.
Don't blame me if you fail
your exams in spring.
It's not just them.
Who exactly am I?
That's not gonna happen.
Hey.
Where are you going?
This is your house, right?
Here?
You're way too out of it.
Will you be all right by yourself?
Should we stick around for a little longer?
You don't have to baby her that much.
You're too harsh.
Um...
I'm going to bed as soon as I get in.
Thank you both for walking me home.
Are you really all right?
Yes.
But...
Hey. Let's go.
Don't drag me.
If anything comes up,
don't hesitate to call.
Get some sleep.
What should I do?
You don't know?
I thought so.
You lost all your memories
from before August 1st.
I did?
I've been with you for four days,
but you don't know who
I am anymore, do you?
I'm sorry.
You seem to be confused
about a lot of things,
so I'll explain everything from the start.
First, let's start with
the introductions.
My name is Orion.
I'm a spirit from a world
separate from this one.
A spirit?
That's right.
Just so you know, only you can see me,
and my voice can't be
heard by others, either.
What? You're looking at
me like I'm an insect.
I don't think you're
an insect or anything.
You had the same reaction
when you first met me.
That's all right, though.
So, actually...
Um...
Well, actually, it's my fault.
I mean, why you lost your memories.
To my surprise,
when I came to this world,
I bumped into your spirit, you know?
It was a real problem for me, too.
I'm really sorry!
What do you mean by that?
In place of the memories that you lost...
In other words, I'm trapped in your soul.
Wait a second.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Wait, why can't I go to the hospital?
Because going to the
hospital won't do any good.
Your memory loss isn't caused by
trouble with your mind or body.
You have to get it back through memories
and interactions shared with others.
If you're hospitalized instead,
and are all alone,
you can't talk to people...
and find the connections
you once had with them.
If that isolation from stimuli continues,
you'll even forget things
like how to drink water,
or how to breathe, and you'll break—
So to make sure that doesn't happen,
we need to avoid thoughtlessly saying
you have amnesia, and act carefully—
But...
I still don't understand anything.
I can't even remember who I am.
Sorry.
Is she really all right?
I wonder if she can make the
trip in her current condition.
Let's just keep an eye on things for now.
I'm counting on you to
cover for her at work.
Of course, that's what
I was planning on doing.
I wonder if Shin and Toma,
the two who walked you home,
work at the same place you do.
They were talking on the way home
like you were childhood friends.
You're right.
But even when they brought up
old stories, you didn't respond,
so I wonder if they suspected something.
Yeah.
Shin
Sawa
Toma
Mie
Meido no Hitsuji
This is all the data I have.
For some reason, all the data
before now was erased.
But it was good that your work
contacts were able to be retrieved.
Yeah.
You might be right, but...
Hey, hey.
Did anything happen today that might
give you a clue to your lost memories?
Why can't I think of anything?
Can I really get my memories back?
Are you all right?
Maybe it's impossible.
Hey, you!
Can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
It's been a tough day,
so you must be tired.
You should go to sleep.
Yeah.
I... I'm going to do my best for you, so...
Good night.
Who am I?
Good morning.
Are your memories from
yesterday still there?
Yes. Somehow.
That's great! So you were
just a little confused.
It seems like your memories
were all mixed up recently,
but maybe you've finally calmed down.
I'm really glad!
If there's anything that troubles
you, you can talk to me.
From your perspective,
you're surrounded by strangers,
and it must be scary not knowing
who you can trust.
But...
But in order to get your memories back,
I'll support you with all my strength.
So, let's do our best together!
Yeah.
Thank you, Orion.
You called me by my name
for the first time!
But this isn't the time for idle chat!
If we don't hurry, you'll be late for work!
I have to go now. Sorry.
Ikki! I'm coming to your café again today!
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Good morning, everyone.
Let's put some energy into
our work again today.
Recently, there have been some
customers who have been
exceedingly rude to our female staff.
If anyone like that comes again today,
please inform me immediately.
I understand.
Worst case, I will murder
them with my own hands.
Wh-What did he just say?
What's he going to do with his hands?
That is all for today's meeting.
Please fulfill your professional
duties again today.
Yes.
He's a strange manager, isn't he?
Hey.
Are you all right to come back?
Yes.
Really?
I'm glad.
Thank you very much...
Is something...
It's time to open.
Ikki-kun, do you have a moment?
Yes.
Let's do our best today, as well.
So he's named Ikki.
Good-looking guy, but kind of shady.
He was looking at you oddly just now.
What is it, manager?
I'll be stepping out for a while.
Do you think so?
I understand.
Welcome.
No, that's not right!
You have to say,
"Welcome back, masters."
The manager is looking over here. Hurry.
Welcome back, masters.
The maid's handmade parfait, please.
I'll have a large mille-feuille
and a Darjeeling tea.
Certainly, masters.
I'll take care of the tea and cake.
Yes. I'll leave it to you.
Isn't the parfait your responsibility?
It is called the maid's handmade, after all.
I'm sorry.
What should I do? I don't
know how to make a parfait.
Oh, no! An order she can't handle already!
Um...
What are you looking for?
Don't tell me you've
forgotten how to make it.
Crap, I think he's suspicious.
Um, I...
Place the flakes into the glass.
Then fresh cream on top.
Then arrange the fruit
and add the ice cream.
And then chocolate on top.
And it's done.
What was that?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Come with me.
This way.
Does it hurt?
But if you tape it tightly,
the bleeding will stop.
Loosen it after a little bit.
All right.
It doesn't work on you, does it?
He was staring at you before, too.
Hey, Ken.
Good morning.
I'm going back to work,
is that all right?
Yes.
Thank you.
See you.
Sorry to make you help me.
Were you the one who induced the
Pauli effect on those glasses?
Pau...?
The Pauli effect.
The theoretical physicist Wolfgang Pauli was
clumsy and often broke equipment.
Apparently, he would sometimes break
tools just by touching or being near them.
Because he broke things so often,
his colleagues teased him,
saying it was due to a mysterious power.
That is the origin of the Pauli effect.
In other words, you are clumsy like Pauli.
That took forever!
And way too indirect.
Furthermore, working
with an injured finger...
can lead to a bacterial infection.
Perhaps you should go home for today.
That's...
We'd like to keep looking, right?
Make up a reason to stay.
Um... Uh...
It's really not a bad injury,
and I'd like to stay...
Yeah, and I've had plenty of rest...
But I'm still no good.
I'd like to get more used to this... So...
Um, I'm an inconvenience, aren't I?
So I'll...
Excuse me.
Could you say what you're
trying to say more logically?
If I could, I'd rather not leave early.
Did I make him angry?
His face is so inexpressive,
I have no idea what he's thinking.
Um... You see, I...
I understand.
You want to become more
used to your job, right?
Then we will back you up.
I'll explain the situation
to the manager.
With that intuitive explanation of yours,
I fear he won't understand.
Please.
Could he have been quiet because he...
was trying to understand
what you were saying?
I see.
If that's the case...
Thank you.
Welcome back, milady.
That was a close call, wasn't it?
S-Sorry.
Be careful.
Right.
Take care, master.
You worked hard today.
Thank you.
Towards the end,
you were doing pretty well.
Do you think so?
Let's work hard tomorrow, too.
Yeah.
Is this...
...me?
You're an eyesore.
A backstabber.
You...
broke your promise, didn't you?
Do you know what "Meido no Hitsuji" means?
"Meido" means underworld,
the realm of Pluto,
["Meido no Hitsuji" ryhmes with "meido to
shitsuji," meaning maids and butlers.]
and "hitsuji" means sheep;
hence, "Pluto's Sheep."
Even so, the maid's handmade parfait
looked delicious, didn't it?
I wish I could eat your handmade parfait.