Don't tell me you've \Nforgotten how to make it.
Crap, I think he's suspicious.
Um, I...
Place the flakes into the glass.
Then fresh cream on top.
Then arrange the fruit \Nand add the ice cream.
And then chocolate on top.
And it's done.
What was that?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Come with me.
This way.
Does it hurt?
But if you tape it tightly, \Nthe bleeding will stop.
Loosen it after a little bit.
All right.
It doesn't work on you, does it?
He was staring at you before, too.
Hey, Ken.
Good morning.
I'm going back to work, \Nis that all right?
Yes.
Thank you.
See you.
Sorry to make you help me.
Were you the one who induced the \NPauli effect on those glasses?
Pau...?
The Pauli effect.
The theoretical physicist Wolfgang Pauli was \Nclumsy and often broke equipment.
Apparently, he would sometimes break \Ntools just by touching or being near them.
Because he broke things so often, \Nhis colleagues teased him,
saying it was due to a mysterious power.
That is the origin of the Pauli effect.
In other words, you are clumsy like Pauli.
That took forever!
And way too indirect.
Furthermore, working \Nwith an injured finger...
can lead to a bacterial infection.
Perhaps you should go home for today.
That's...
We'd like to keep looking, right?
Make up a reason to stay.
Um... Uh...
It's really not a bad injury, \Nand I'd like to stay...
Yeah, and I've had plenty of rest...
But I'm still no good.
I'd like to get more used to this... So...
Um, I'm an inconvenience, aren't I?
So I'll...
Excuse me.
Could you say what you're \Ntrying to say more logically?
If I could, I'd rather not leave early.
Did I make him angry?
His face is so inexpressive,\NI have no idea what he's thinking.
Um... You see, I...
I understand.
You want to become more \Nused to your job, right?
Then we will back you up.
I'll explain the situation \Nto the manager.
With that intuitive explanation of yours,
I fear he won't understand.
Please.
Could he have been quiet because he...
was trying to understand \Nwhat you were saying?
I see.
If that's the case...
Thank you.
Welcome back, milady.
That was a close call, wasn't it?
S-Sorry.